hello good afternoon welcome thanks for
你好，下午好，欢迎感谢
coming to my talk my name is Stuart
来我的谈话我叫斯图尔特
marks I'm also known as dr. deprecated
我也被称为博士。不推荐使用
er I work on the JDK core libraries team
我在JDK核心库团队中工作
at Oracle so the talk today is about
在Oracle，所以今天的话题是
enhanced deprecation i'm going to give
我将给予更高的折旧费
brief history of the concept and and
该概念的简要历史，以及
history of deprecation but there's been
弃用的历史，但有
a lot of work on deprecation and I've
关于折旧的很多工作，我已经
done I've done most of that work in jdk
完成了我在jdk中完成的大部分工作
9v there's a lot of work in progress and
9v正在进行很多工作，
most of that work is understanding how
大部分工作是了解
notification and warnings occur and what
通知和警告发生以及什么
purpose they serve and the policies
他们服务的目的和政策
around though so I'll speak spending
虽然，所以我会说支出
some time talking about the details of
有一段时间谈论的细节
that and then that's a little odd I'm
那然后有点奇怪我
last bullets supposed to be future work
最后的子弹应该是未来的工作
so there's a bunch of work going on in
所以有很多工作要做
jdk 9 and then there's there's some
jdk 9，然后有一些
future work beyond that so there is a
以后的工作，因此有一个
twitter hashtag for this talk enhanced
此演讲的twitter标签
deprecation if you have follow-up
如果您需要跟进，则弃用
questions or comments please please
问题或意见，请
tweet with that hashtag alright so let's
与该标签一起发推，好吧，让我们
step back a little bit and look at the
退后一点，看看
the systems development life cycle so
系统开发生命周期
this is one of these one of these
这是这些之一
diagrams with all these different phases
所有这些不同阶段的图表
I pulled this off of Wikipedia it's
我从维基百科上摘下来的是
pretty conventional you start something
很传统，你开始做某事
you develop it you you know it gets
你开发它，你知道它得到
reviewed it gets it gets goes through
审查它得到它得到通过
iterations it gets put into productions
迭代投入生产
and so forth and then there's what
等等，然后是什么
happens to the very end and they call
发生到最后，他们打电话
this phase disposition and extremely
这个阶段的性格和极端
little attention is paid to the end of a
很少注意到结尾
systems lifecycle and that's what
系统生命周期，这就是事实
deprecation is about and in Java we are
弃用即将发生，在Java中，
in the in the JDK group we are really
在JDK小组中，我们确实
looking at the Java platform in the long
长期来看Java平台
term and so we are starting to pay more
学期，所以我们开始支付更多
attention to the end of the life cycle
注意生命周期的结束
most of the talks you've probably been
您可能参加过的大多数谈话
to here at javaone or about something
到这里在javaone或关于什么
new something is new and exciting and
新的东西是新的，令人兴奋的，
different and that's great I think we
不同，那太好了，我认为我们
all love that stuff but something has to
所有人都喜欢那东西，但必须
be done with old stuff and so that's
用旧的东西完成，所以
what this talk is about
这个话题是关于什么
so let me talk about the life cycle of
所以我来谈谈生命周期
an API as distinct from the life cycle
与生命周期截然不同的API
of a product perhaps many of you
一种产品也许你们中的许多人
familiar with the idea of a product you
熟悉您对产品的想法
you you put in it production it goes
你把它投入生产
through some support there bug fixes and
通过一些支持，那里有错误修复和
then over time the number of bug fixes
然后随着时间的推移，错误修复的数量
trails off and only critical or
落后，只有关键或
showstopper bugs get fixed then maybe
showstopper错误得到修复，然后也许
only security holes of the of the
的仅安全漏洞
greatest urgency but at a certain point
最大的紧迫性，但在某些时候
then it's it's retired if you're
那就是如果你退休了
shipping a commercial software product
运送商业软件产品
what happens is it goes through
发生了什么事
end-of-life process like end of support
寿命终止过程（如支持终止）
life after which there are fewer and
生命过后，
fewer bug fix releases after which
在此之后，较少的错误修复版本
there's complete end of support it's not
没有完全的支持，不是
supported anymore now the lifecycle of
现在支持了生命周期
an API is kind of different the same
API有点不同
thing sort of happens over time except
事情会随着时间的推移发生
that it occurs in successive releases of
它发生在
the Java platform and so if you look at
Java平台，所以如果您看一下
releases of the Java platform you know
您知道的Java平台版本
JDK 1 2 3 4 5 and up we're working on JD
JDK 1 2 3 4 5及更高版本，我们正在开发JD
k9 now life the life cycle of an API
k9现在生活在API的生命周期中
might get introduced at one point in a
可能会在一处被介绍
jdk release live for several releases
JDK实时发布了多个版本
and then be retired but the the jdk
然后退休，但jdk
itself and the java platform continue on
本身和Java平台继续
successive releases so it's really the
连续发行，所以实际上
introduction of an api followed by its
api的介绍，然后是其
life and support and perhaps bug fixes
生活和支持以及错误修复
and then the removal of the feature from
然后从中删除该功能
the java platform although the platform
java平台虽然平台
itself continues on ok key concept of
本身继续确定的关键概念
deprecation is the designer and the
弃用的是设计师和
maintainer of the API communicating to
与API通信的维护者
you the developers or the consumers of
您是开发商或消费者
the API information about what is going
有关正在发生的事情的API信息
on with that API and in particular when
使用该API，尤其是当
the API is starting to reach the end of
该API开始到达末尾
its lifetime deprecation is a way for
它的生命周期弃用是
the maintainer to say ok you should
维护者说好，你应该
start thinking differently about this
开始对此有所不同的思考
API and your usage of it and so one of
API及其使用情况，其中之一
the one of the ways that you should take
你应该采取的方式之一
action if you're using deprecated API is
如果您使用的API已弃用，则该操作是
is you should start considering
你应该开始考虑吗
migrating away from it
从那里迁移
there might be some several reasons why
可能有几个原因
we might why we might decide to ramp
我们可能为什么我们可能决定增加
down support or even eventually remove
向下支持甚至最终删除
ap is from from the JDK and one is
ap来自JDK，一个来自
there's something wrong with it and so
这有什么问题，所以
if you're using that API you should you
如果您正在使用该API，则应该
should be notified of what's going on so
应该被告知发生了什么事情
you should understand what's what's
你应该明白什么是什么
wrong with it or what are the risks of
错误或有什么风险
using it sometimes we've introduced a
使用它有时我们引入了
new or better API and your programs will
新的或更好的API，您的程序将
run better faster higher quality more
运行更好更快质量更高
lively or whatever using this new API
生动活泼或使用此新API的任何东西
instead of this older one so that's
而不是这个较旧的那个
another form of notification and then
另一种形式的通知，然后
finally if we are intending to remove an
最后，如果我们打算删除
API from the JDK entirely then that's a
完全来自JDK的API，那么
very serious step and that will actually
非常认真的一步，实际上
break programs and so there is an even
中断程序，所以有一个偶数
stronger form of notification that needs
需要的更强大的通知形式
to occur there because we don't want
在那里发生，因为我们不想
people to be surprised by the program's
人们对该程序的惊讶
breaking all right so let's let's move
打破所有权利，让我们开始吧
away from the basic concepts here and
远离这里的基本概念，
talk about some some history so
说说一些历史
deprecation was introduced in jdk 1.1
JDK 1.1中引入了弃用
and there were no annotations at that
而且没有注释
time annotations didn't come for several
时间注释没有来了好几次
years later and so the way this was
几年后，所以这是
introduced was as a javadoc tag at
引入是作为javadoc标签在
deprecated with a with a small initial d
不推荐使用带有较小首字母d的a
now what's interesting is there's so
现在有趣的是
much oral history around this so so this
关于这个的很多口述历史
original deprecation work was was done
原来的折旧工作已经完成
by John Rose who is now the JVM
现在是JVM的John Rose
architect and he may have seen talks
建筑师，他可能看过讲座
about him this conference or materials
关于他的这次会议或材料
by him he's doing project Valhalla and
他在做Valhalla项目，
project Panama now anyway so I was at
现在无论如何要计划巴拿马，所以我当时在
dinner with him last night and we were
昨晚和他共进晚餐，我们
talking about you know so how's your
谈论你知道所以你怎么样
talks going and I said oh I have a
会谈，我说哦，我有一个
deprecation talk and of course I knew he
弃用话题，我当然知道他
I I've known him for several years he
我认识他已有几年了
says oh that's right yeah I remember he
说哦，是的，是的，我记得他
says I remember putting the deprecation
说我记得过时了
stuff in he was he was the new guy in
他是他的新人
Java at the time and the reason
当时的Java及其原因
deprecation was put in was james gosling
詹姆斯·高斯林（James Gosling）被弃用了
the orig
原始
of Java had some misgivings about api's
Java语言对api有一些疑虑
that were in the platform and he was
在平台上，他是
worried wanted to do something about it
担心要对此做些什么
and so they came up with this idea okay
所以他们想出了这个主意
well if there's like if there's a
好吧，如果有的话
concern about this API then we need to
关注此API，那么我们需要
say something about it it should be
说些什么
deprecated and that's that's where this
不赞成使用，那就是这个地方
originated and so anyway so in 1.1 the
起源，所以无论如何在1.1中
deprecation mechanism was introduced
引入了弃用机制
this is Javadoc tag and then there was
这是Javadoc标签，然后
an initial massive wave of defecation so
最初的排便浪潮如此
some some api's such as thread destroy
一些API，例如线程破坏
it's impossible to use thread destroy
使用线程破坏是不可能的
safely now it's not not actually
现在安全地不是真的
implemented but the the intent was that
已实施，但目的是
the that if that if a thread is running
如果线程正在运行
that it be simply stopped in its tracks
只是停在自己的轨道上
no well anyway so it's impossible for
反正不好，所以不可能
forget if it was ever implemented I
忘记是否曾经实施过
forget whether what it actually did but
忘记它实际上做了什么，但是
it's impossible to use that safely and
安全地使用它是不可能的，
so that that was mark deprecated and
因此，该标记已被弃用，
then there was a long explanation which
然后有一个很长的解释
I think John Rose wrote which was theirs
我想约翰·罗斯（John Rose）写的是他们的
you can still find it in the Javadoc yr
您仍然可以在Javadoc yr中找到它
destroy stop and suspend and resume
破坏停止，暂停并继续
deprecated but then deprecation was used
弃用，但随后使用弃用
for an entirely different reason so the
由于完全不同的原因，所以
the guys who were working on the desktop
在桌面上工作的家伙
at the time was a TBT those desktop
当时是TBT那些台式机
api's they decided okay well we had and
api他们决定好吧，我们有
we have a component class and you can
我们有一个组件类，您可以
show a component and you can hide a
显示一个组件，您可以隐藏一个
component but in order to make it
组件，但为了使它
compatible with netbeans sorry not that
与netbeans兼容对不起
means javabeans in order to make it
意思是为了使它成为javabeans
compatible with javabeans the idea was
与javabeans兼容的想法是
to set a property and so they said okay
设置财产，所以他们说还可以
instead of showing hide let's change
而不是显示隐藏，让我们改变
change those two setvisible true or
更改这两个setvisible true或
false and so they deprecated show and
错误，因此他们弃用了show和
hide now there's nothing at all wrong
现在隐藏，没有任何错误
with showing hi there was not dangerous
向大家打招呼并不危险
at all and in fact people who customize
根本上，实际上是那些自定义的人
components / road show and hide so those
组件/路演和隐藏等
those those methods ended up it was
那些方法最终导致了
impossible to remove him without
没有他就无法删除他
breaking compatibility so the problem
破坏兼容性的问题
was that a lot of things in the JDK got
在JDK中有很多东西
deprecated very quickly and it caused a
很快就弃用了，这导致了
lot of disruption
很多破坏
and deprecation caused introduced
和过时引起的介绍
compiler warnings and so there was
编译器警告，所以有
massive concern because people
引起广泛关注，因为人们
recompiled the program's got lots of
重新编译该程序的很多
warnings and they said oh no what's
警告，他们说哦，不，这是什么
going on with that so we put the brakes
继续下去，所以我们刹车了
on everything so don't deprecated
一切都不要过时
anything else after that and there was
在那之后的任何其他事情
the the rate of deprecation slowed down
弃用率减慢了
considerably and in fact nothing was
相当多，实际上什么也没有
ever removed because of the initial
由于最初被删除
reaction of you know don't get rid of
你的反应知道你不会摆脱
all that stuff so that situation remain
所有这些东西，以便保持现状
consistent for a long time until Java
直到Java一直保持一致
five now the some mechanics of
五现在的一些机制
deprecation were changed in Java five
Java 5中弃用已更改
because the annotation mechanism was
因为注释机制是
introduced and so instead of having a
介绍，所以而不是有一个
javadoc tag in a comment affect the
注释中的javadoc标记会影响
compilation of program which you think
您认为程序的汇编
about is a very strange thing an
关于是一件很奇怪的事情
annotation is a more formal way that's
注释是一种更正式的方式
part of the language that that allows
允许使用的语言的一部分
you to provide meta information about an
您提供有关
API and so from that standpoint oh ok
API，从这个角度来看，好吧
this is this is a way to to to provide
这是提供的一种方式
meta information about an API that says
有关说明以下内容的API的元信息
it is deprecated so deprecation as an
不推荐使用，因此不推荐使用
annotation and since annotations are
注释，因为注释是
classes they begin with a capital D so
他们以大写D开头的类
we have the lowercase deprecated Javadoc
我们已经使用了小写的Javadoc
tag and the uppercase annotation so
标签和大写注解，因此
those are both present and annotation is
这些都存在并且注释是
is the formal way to declare an API
是声明API的正式方法
deprecated but there was actually no
已弃用，但实际上没有
clarification of this business about
关于此业务的澄清
well what's going to happen to these
那么这些将会发生什么
deprecated api's are they going to be
不推荐使用的api是
removed how do we deal with these
删除了我们如何处理这些
compiler warnings and stuff there was a
编译器警告和其他东西
suppress warnings annotation added as
禁止添加警告注释
well that allowed allowing programmers
好让程序员
to control compiler warnings so I want
控制编译器警告，所以我想
to take a quick aside to share with you
快速分享给您
some some deprecation trivia which at
一些弃用琐事
least I find interesting there's a case
至少我觉得有趣
where something was under cated the
哪里遇到了麻烦
there's a method called system get end
有一种方法叫做system get end
which has a particularly tortured
受到特别折磨
history in in jdk
JDK中的历史
and in fact it did nothing except throw
实际上除了丢球什么也没做
and throw an exception unconditionally
并无条件抛出异常
and as Java doc said obsolete so it's
而且正如Java文档所说的过时一样，
kind of interesting to have something
有一些有趣的事
appear in one point oh and be documented
一口气出现并被记录在案
as obsolete and and my belief is I
过时了，我的信念是
haven't confirmed this but my belief is
尚未确认，但我的信念是
that at the time the people who were
当时的人
working on Java wanted wanted to make it
在Java上工作的人想要实现它
impossible to write a program that was
不可能写一个程序是
platform specific and the environment is
具体平台和环境
very OS specific but I think over the
非常特定于操作系统，但我认为
years practical reality intervened and
多年的实践现实介入并
by Java five an actual get end of
通过Java五实际结束
implementation which looked at the
实施，着眼于
respective platforms environment
各自的平台环境
variables and return them was introduced
变量并返回它们被介绍
and that method was actually under cated
而这种方法实际上没有得到满足
and so it is now a fully supported part
所以现在它是一个完全受支持的部分
of the API now Gannon was not introduced
API的现在不引入Gannon
as deprecated because deprecation did
之所以弃用，是因为弃用
not exist in one point oh so has
一站式不存在哦
anything ever been introduced and
曾经介绍过的任何东西
deprecated when it was introduced answer
引入时已弃用答案
yes so there's an mbean server in Java X
是的，因此Java X中有一个mbean服务器
management that appeared initially in
最初出现在
java SE 5 and it was first deprecated in
Java SE 5，它最早在
java SE 5 so that's that's pretty
Java SE 5就是这样
strange but but the reason for that is
奇怪，但是原因是
that the the jmx stuff was a separate
jmx的东西是一个单独的
jsr and so it had a separate standalone
jsr，所以它有一个独立的
set of api's through their evolution
通过它们的演变形成的一组api
process something's got deprecated and
处理已弃用的东西，
then those were migrated into java SE as
然后将它们迁移到Java SE
of java SE 5 but it looks strange from
SE 5的代码，但从
the java SE standpoint because something
Java SE的观点是因为
was introduced and deprecated at the
在引入和弃用
same time all right so I wanted to go
同时还好，所以我想去
back to what I was saying about this
回到我所说的
confusion about what deprecation really
究竟是什么贬值感到困惑
meant and I think that that existed that
的意思，我认为那是存在的
existed for many years and up through
存在多年，直到
and including Java 8 I will still see
包括Java 8我仍然会看到
comments when people will say this on
人们何时会对此发表评论
internet forums and whatnot somebody
互联网论坛等等
will say hey I use this and it I'm
会说嘿，我用这个，我
getting this deprecation warning what
得到此折旧警告是什么
does this mean and there are two flavors
这是否意味着有两种口味
of ants I mean a bunch of answers of
蚂蚁，我的意思是一堆答案
course but they're two flavors of
当然，但是它们是两种
answers somebody will say all that
答案有人会说所有
deprecation stuff just ignore that it
弃用的东西只是忽略它
doesn't make any difference they will
他们不会有任何不同
never remove anything but then other
从不删除任何东西，但其他
people will say no no deprecation means
人们会说没有否决手段
they're going to remove it so don't use
他们将要删除它，所以不要使用
that
那
and and then people would argue about
然后人们会争论
what deprecation means and the problem
弃用是什么意思和问题
is that you know that you can't say
是你知道你不能说
whether whether either of those
是否这些
statements is right or wrong because we
陈述是对还是错，因为我们
as the maintainer of the platform never
作为平台的维护者
clarified it and so that's my job so
弄清楚了，这就是我的工作，所以
that's what we're doing in Java nine
这就是我们在Java 9中所做的
here in particular 11 I'd wanted to you
这里特别是11我想要你
know finally we're getting to the point
知道最后我们到了重点
where we're paying attention to this one
我们正在关注这一点
of the statements is made it has been
的陈述是已经
made is oh those guys that Sun and
哦，太阳和
Oracle have never removed anything from
Oracle从未删除过任何内容
the platform and they never will wrong
平台，他们永远不会错
in Java 9 we're actually starting to
在Java 9中，我们实际上开始
remove stuff and so all right all right
删除东西，所以好吧好吧
round of applause for removals okay that
一阵热烈的掌声
I didn't expect that thank you so most
没想到我会非常感谢你
of the motivation for these removals
这些清除的动机
were to remove dependencies across
被删除依赖
modules and so you probably heard a lot
模块，所以您可能听到很多
of things about modularization and
关于模块化和
project jigsaw and you can talk about
项目拼图，你可以谈谈
modules and interdependencies and stuff
模块和相互依存关系
and these ap is created new dependencies
这些ap被创建了新的依赖项
between modules that we did not want to
在我们不想使用的模块之间
have and I think Mark Ryan holder might
有，我认为Mark Ryan持有人可能
have actually mentioned that in the
实际上在
keynote so anyway so these are the
所以无论如何主题演讲都是
things that were moved in Java 94 for
在Java 94中为
that purpose there were some other
这个目的还有其他
errors we also corrected so in the awt
我们也在awt中更正了错误
API there's a concept of peers and in
API中有一个对等的概念
fact some of the types that those API is
实际上这些API的某些类型
used were in an API that was not
使用的是不是
actually part of java SE so how can you
实际上是Java SE的一部分，那么您怎么能
write a portable application if it has a
如果有便携式应用程序，请编写
type that's not actually defined as part
实际上没有定义为一部分的类型
of java SE so that's really a
SE SE的代码，所以实际上
long-standing error in the specification
规范中的长期错误
because the specification is not is not
因为规格不是
complete by itself it refers to
完全完成是指
something outside of itself in in an
自身之外的东西
uncontrolled way so we we actually and
不受控制的方式，所以我们实际上和
in fact peers we're never supposed to be
实际上，我们从来都不应该成为同龄人
public API anyway so we also remove
无论如何，我们还是要删除公共API
those in Java nine all right so now
Java 9的人现在可以了
getting getting up to the present what
起床到现在
what's been done I think the
我认为做了什么
there's this relatively little software
这个软件比较少
engineering as part of deprecation it's
工程是弃用的一部分
not like I wrote thousands of lines of
不像我写了数千行
code for this I did write some code for
为此的代码我确实写了一些代码
this but but relatively not that much
这个但相对不那么多
the major work here is the clarification
这里的主要工作是澄清
of semantics and what does deprecation
语义和弃用是什么
mean and and most importantly I think
意思是，最重要的是，我认为
what should developers do if they find
开发人员发现后应该怎么做
that they are using deprecated API and
他们使用的API已弃用，并且
so that's where most of the work is
所以那是大部分工作的地方
there are some enhancements to the
有一些增强
deprecated annotation itself there are
不推荐使用的注释本身
two they're kind of like parameters
两个他们有点像参数
they're formally called elements but
它们被正式称为元素，但是
there's a since element which is a
有一个since元素，它是一个
string value which which which records
记录的字符串值
the release in which the in which that
在哪个版本中
API became deprecated but more important
API已弃用，但更重要
i think is this new boolean element for
我认为这是新的布尔元素
removal and what that says is if it's
删除，这是说，如果
actually cover that on the next slide
实际在下一张幻灯片中介绍
okay so so there are some enhancements
好，所以有一些增强
to the deprecated annotation I'll get to
到不赞成使用的注释
those more detail later we're also
那些更多的细节，我们也
introducing a new static analysis tool
引入新的静态分析工具
called JD purse can I will cover what
叫JD钱包，我可以涵盖什么
that does somewhat later and then there
稍后再做
are some adjustments to the Java
是对Java的一些调整
language specification Java C and Java
语言规范Java C和Java
doc in order to in order to refine their
doc为了以完善自己
treatment of the deprecated annotation
不推荐使用的注释的处理
all right so here's what here's the
好吧，这就是这里的
details on on the new deprecation
有关新折旧的详细信息
elements and so I think for removal
元素，所以我想删除
really is the main the most important
真的是最主要的
thing I mean it's all it is as a boolean
我的意思是，这就是布尔值
but it's it's amazing how much
但令人惊讶的是
discussion took place in the background
讨论在后台进行
and all that got added was a boolean but
而所有添加的是布尔值，
it's very important because that
这很重要，因为
discussion improved everybody's
讨论改善了每个人的
understanding of what deprecation was
了解什么是弃用
but basically that that that that
但基本上那个
hypothetical art well not hypothetical
假想的艺术而不是假想的
but the kind of prototypical argument I
但是我的原型论证
was talking about they're never going to
在谈论他们永远不会
remove anything what does deprecation
删除任何不赞成使用的东西
mean should I be worried about about
意思是我应该担心
removing it or should I be worried that
删除它，否则我应该担心
that I'm using
我正在使用
deprecated API will it be removed or not
不推荐使用的API是否将其删除
that's what this says so if for removal
这就是这个意思，所以如果要移除
is true then this means that whoever is
是真的，那就意味着无论是谁
maintaining this API is saying yes this
维持这个API就是说这个
is going to be removed it doesn't say
将被删除，它没有说
when it's going to be removed but in the
当它要被删除，但在
JDK what we're trying to say is if
JDK我们要说的是
something is deprecated for removal in
不建议将某些东西移除
this release then it will be removed
此版本，然后它将被删除
from the next release so that's what
从下一个版本开始就是这样
we're trying to say so we give one
我们试图说，所以我们给一个
release warning before we remove
在移除之前发布警告
something I'm I'm sorry what was oh yes
抱歉，对不起，是的
major releases yes so okay thank you
是的，主要发行版本是这样，谢谢
yeah so if something is deprecated for
是的，所以如果某些东西不推荐使用
removal in this release the it will be
在此版本中删除它将是
removed in the next major release or
在下一个主要版本中删除，或
than in in the JDK at least major
至少在JDK中
releases are the only releases where we
版本是我们唯一的版本
actually make specification changes okay
实际上可以进行规格更改
and so so adding a deprecation is a
所以添加弃用是一个
specification change and of course
规格变更，当然
removing an API is also a specification
删除API也是一个规范
change ok so for removal false well what
更改确定，以便删除错误以及什么
you know why is something deprecated if
你知道为什么有些东西不赞成
you're not going to remove it well there
你不会在那里很好地删除它
are lots of things where it's not
很多东西不是
necessary to remove them but still there
有必要删除它们，但仍然在那里
are it's still useful for people to know
人们知道它仍然有用吗
that that this API has something wrong
该API有问题
with it or there's there's something
有了它，或者有东西
else to be used and so in fact there are
其他要用的，所以实际上有
many more deprecation 'he's with for
他弃用了更多
removal false then there are four with
去除假然后有四个
for removal true and so there's some old
去除真，所以有一些旧
AP is that you're better off using
AP是您最好使用
something else but we're leaving them in
其他的东西，但我们留给他们
the platform just because we don't want
该平台只是因为我们不想
to break people's code and so so there's
破坏人们的密码，所以
a little bit of clumsiness hear about
有点笨拙听到
the wording and so we've cooked up some
措辞，所以我们煮了一些
some terminology here if something is
这里有些术语，如果有的话
deprecated with for removal false that's
不建议使用，以将false删除
an ordinary deprecation but if for
普通的折旧，但如果
removal is true we're calling that a
删除是真的，我们称之为
terminal deprecation because it implies
最终弃用，因为这意味着
you know something is something is going
你知道某事正在发生
to end so it makes it a little easier to
结束，这使得它更容易
talk about it
说说它
so basically if something is deprecated
所以基本上，如果某些东西被弃用
for removal false that is if it has an
如果它有一个
ordinary deprecation that means there's
普通的贬值意味着
no current intent to remove it doesn't
目前没有删除它的意图
mean it's going to stay forever but if
意味着它将永远存在，但是如果
we do decide to to remove it in the
我们确实决定将其删除
future then the the for removal will be
未来，那么将被删除
upgraded from false it's true go ahead
从错误升级，这是真的，继续
question ah yes the default value is
问题ah是，默认值为
false so all pre-existing deprecation
错误，因此所有先前存在的折旧
are by default for removal false their
默认情况下会删除false
ordinary deprecation so what we've done
普通的弃用，所以我们已经做了
is we've taken I what I did is I went
是我们带走了我所做的就是我去了
through all of the old deprecated not
通过所有旧的过时不
all of the old I went through many of
我经历过的所有旧事
the old deprecated api's and re-examined
旧的已弃用的api并重新检查
them and said okay these are the ones we
他们说，好的，这些是我们
really are going to remove and then I
真的要删除，然后我
left old deprecated API is that we have
剩下的旧的不推荐使用的API是
no intent to remove I left those as
无意删除我离开那些作为
false okay so and then I also mentioned
假好吧，然后我也提到了
since having a string value which is the
因为有一个字符串值是
release in which something became
释放其中变成了某种东西
deprecated i think i want to take I'll
不赞成使用，我想我要接受
take questions at the end thank you and
最后提问，谢谢
mostly this is informational there's no
大部分这是信息性的，没有
as far as I know there's no no semantics
据我所知，没有语义
attached to what string gets foot there
附着在什么弦上
but it's useful to see when something
但是看什么时候很有用
was deprecated now quick quick aside any
现在已弃用
some of you might have seen previous
你们中有些人可能以前见过
proposals of about deprecation where
关于弃用的建议
there was a there was a reason tag and
有一个原因标签，
new value in particular the one that
新价值，特别是
attracted the most attention was
引起最多关注的是
condemned there were also other values
谴责还有其他价值
superseded obsolete dangerous and so
取代过时的危险等等
forth and so that was an earlier version
来了，所以这是一个较早的版本
of the of the proposal and it turned out
提案的结果，结果
that having a reason code there is nice
有一个原因码很好
it generated a lot of discussion I think
我认为这引起了很多讨论
the semantics were were good but they
语义很好，但是它们
were not really well defined so it
定义不是很好，所以它
didn't make sense for there to be a
没有意义的是
specific reason in in the API saying why
API中的特定原因说明原因
this is deprecated or what would happen
这已被弃用或将会发生什么
to it so in fact the problem was we knew
为此，实际上问题是我们知道
we wanted to deprecate something we we
我们想弃用我们
actually spent some time trying to
实际上花了一些时间尝试
assign a reason code
分配原因码
and it was basically impossible so maybe
基本上是不可能的，所以也许
that told us there's something wrong
告诉我们出了点问题
with the API so really condemned is the
与API，因此真正受到谴责的是
only one that is strictly actionable it
只有一个是严格可行的
has a clear semantic meaning so we just
具有明确的语义，所以我们只是
converted that into so condemned got
转换成如此谴责的
converted into the for removal boolean
转换为for移除布尔值
and then the rest of those concepts are
然后剩下的那些概念是
valid concepts they're simply not in the
有效概念，它们根本不在
API and we're saying well if you have
API，如果您有的话，我们说的很好
something that is dangerous then instead
然后是危险的东西
of marking it as dangerous and having
将其标记为危险并具有
people saying well what does that mean
人们说的好是什么意思
that belongs in the documentation if
属于文档，如果
something is dangerous or risky then as
有危险或危险的东西
the API designer you or we I mean we're
API设计师您或我们，我是说我们
designing a lot of the api's but anybody
设计很多的api，但是任何人
who uses the deprecated annotation and
谁使用了已弃用的注释，并且
you know there's a there might be a risk
你知道那里可能有风险
associated with this API because it
与此API相关联，因为它
might give the wrong answer in some
在某些情况下可能会给出错误的答案
cases or or something like that so that
案件或类似的东西
shouldn't that's really that's really
那不应该是真的吗
part of the documentation as opposed to
文档的一部分，而不是
something that belongs in the annotation
注释中包含的内容
all right so what if we what have we
好吧，如果我们有什么
done in Java nine so far so these are
到目前为止，用Java九完成了这些
ordinary deprecation for removal false
普通的过时去除假
the boxed primitive constructors new
盒装的基本构造函数new
integer new boolean new short new new
整数new boolean new short new new
double new floated Sarah all of those
双重新的莎拉所有这些
have been deprecated in most cases those
在大多数情况下已被弃用
can simply be replaced by the
可以简单地用
corresponding value of method
方法的对应值
particularly for things like boolean
特别是对于布尔值
there are only two boolean value box
只有两个布尔值框
boolean values and so there's never a
布尔值，因此永远不会
reason to to create a new instance of a
创建一个新实例的理由
boolean but people do things like that
布尔值，但人们这样做
in order to in order to lock on it or
为了锁定它或
something like that it's like really bad
这样的事情真的很糟糕
idea we did have one case in the JDK
我们在JDK中确实有一个案例
that used a boolean field as a tri-state
使用布尔字段作为三态的
no true and false so I think we got rid
没有对与错，所以我认为我们摆脱了
of that too so there's a long story with
其中也有一个很长的故事
Java applet if you've been following
Java applet（如果您一直关注）
applets in the browser plug-in those
浏览器插件中的小程序
have been on their way out for a very
已经走了很长时间
long time but it turns out that this is
很长一段时间，但事实证明这是
a very slow evolution and so many so so
进化非常缓慢，如此之多
people are I think are not surprised
我认为人们并不感到惊讶
that applets are being deprecated but
小应用程序已被弃用，但
what they are surprised by is applets
他们惊讶的是小程序
are
是
marked for removal and I had a
标记为删除，我有一个
discussion with the the desktop team
与桌面团队讨论
about this it's like what what you know
关于这就像你所知道的
what should the deprecation be are you
你应该弃用什么
intending to move it they also know yeah
打算搬家，他们也知道
we're going to get rid of it okay right
我们将摆脱它，好吧
I said okay you're going to get rid of
我说好的，你要摆脱
in the next release um well maybe
在下一个版本中，嗯，也许
actually there are other people oh we
其实还有其他人哦，我们
have this customer who's still using
有这个还在使用的客户
their they going to get up so there's a
他们他们要起床，所以有一个
bunch of hemming and hawing about it
一堆关于它的折边
right and so you know a minute and then
对，所以你知道一分钟，然后
they started you got uncomfortable yeah
他们开始让你感到不舒服耶
I don't think we can move it remove it
我认为我们无法将其移除
the next release so that's the kind of
下一个版本，这就是
thing that goes on so so the fact is
事情如此继续，所以事实是
applets are on their way out but they're
小程序正在出路，但它们
still around because they still get used
还在附近，因为他们仍然习惯
so applets are being deprecated but with
所以小程序被弃用了，但是
for removal false there's an there's a
去除假有一个
vestige of a very old event observation
一个非常古老的事件观察的痕迹
model in Java util observer and
Java util观察器中的模型和
observable I don't know if anybody uses
可观察的，我不知道是否有人使用
these there turns out was it I forget
这些原来是我忘记了
never mind i did actually hear of some
没关系，我确实听说过一些
some some use of these because he
一些这些用途，因为他
created a bunch of compiler warnings
创建了一堆编译器警告
when this became deprecated but really
当它被弃用，但实际上
these these are there much better
这些这些都好多了
alternatives to using observer and
使用观察者的替代方法和
observable in fact when when i mentioned
事实上，当我提到
this the people you know people that
这个你认识的人
most people have never heard of these
大多数人从未听说过这些
all right what things are we deprecating
好吧，我们正在贬低什么东西
for removal so so now for these things
为了去除所以现在这些东西
in java nine they are still going to be
在Java九中，它们仍将是
there that are going to be annotated
那里将要被注释
with at deprecated for removal equals
不推荐使用的at等于
true which means the plan is in java 10
true，表示该计划在Java 10中
that these will be gone okay so thread
这些将消失，所以线程
destroy that's that's that's going away
消灭那就是那消逝
now there is there are two overloads of
现在有两个重载
thread dot stop one of them takes a
线程点停止其中之一需要一个
throwable argument that that causes that
引发该问题的可抛出参数
causes the thread to be stopped in its
导致线程在其中停止
tracks and a throw to throw the
轨道和一掷一掷
throwable of the caller's choosing and
投掷者的选择和
in fact that was actually disabled in
事实上，实际上是在
Java 8 so that does not work anymore and
Java 8，使其不再起作用，并且
so we actually have not heard any
所以我们实际上没有听到
complaints about that so far as i know
据我所知
so we're going to get rid of that now
所以我们现在要摆脱它
the
的
the thread dot stop overload with no
线程点停止过载，没有
argument is still deprecated but we are
争论仍然不赞成，但我们
not going to remove that so that stays
不会删除它，以便保持
there so there's an interesting story
那里有一个有趣的故事
with this this this other method here
有了这个这另一种方法
system dot run finalize errs on exit and
系统点运行在退出时终结错误，然后
so somebody who you know I don't know if
所以你认识的人我不知道
you if you're familiar with finalization
如果您熟悉定稿，则为您
and all that was something that's a that
而所有的事情就是
that's that's been a facility in the
那是过去的设施
platform for for many years somebody
平台多年有人
thought it would be a good idea so that
认为这是一个好主意，所以
to have a flag that said when the system
有一个标志，说当系统
is exiting well we want to do some
顺利退出，我们想做一些
cleanup so run all the finalizer
清理，所以运行所有终结器
unconditionally unfortunately this means
不幸的是，这意味着
that finalize errs will get run on live
最终确定错误将实时运行
objects and if a live object has some
对象，如果有生命的对象有一些
native resources associated with it then
然后与之关联的本地资源
quite rightly that finalizar will say oh
没错，finalizar会说哦
okay i can free those native resources
好吧，我可以释放这些本机资源
unfortunately there's no control over
不幸的是，无法控制
the ordering of finalizer calls and so
终结器调用的顺序等
something else some other finalizer
其他一些终结器
might say might call back into that that
可能会说回
first class that had a native resource
具有本地资源的头等舱
which has already been freed and so it
已经被释放了，所以它
makes a native call finds that something
拨打本地电话后发现
has been freed and causes the vm to
已被释放并导致虚拟机
crash and so I think when is the yes in
崩溃，所以我认为什么时候是
1999 people discovered this and so there
1999年人们发现了这个，所以在那里
was a conformance failure because the
是一致性失败，因为
system crashes when we call this we have
系统崩溃时我们称之为
we have a test program that will crash
我们有一个会崩溃的测试程序
the JVM every single time how do we fix
JVM每次如何修复
this well the only way to fix it is to
修复它的唯一方法是
get rid of it so well finally going to
好好摆脱它终于要
fix this bug by removing the API and in
通过删除API并修复此错误
fact the semantics of run finalized errs
实际上，run最终错误的语义
on exit are simply incorrect because the
退出时根本不正确，因为
finalizer should only be run on an
终结器只能在
object that is unreachable but this says
无法访问的对象，但这说
oh by the way we're going to run
哦，顺便说一句，我们要运行
finalizer zon live object so anyway so
finalizer zon活动对象，所以无论如何
that's that's leaving and then finally
那就是要走了，然后终于
there are a whole pile of methods on
有很多方法
security manager that are going to be
安全经理将
removed those are vestiges of the pre
删除了那些是前
1.2 security model and so in jdk 1.2 the
1.2安全性模型等等在jdk 1.2中
permissions based security model came in
基于权限的安全模型
but there are all these old check
但是所有这些旧支票
permissions stuff left on security
权限问题留给安全性
manager and we are finally getting rid
经理，我们终于摆脱了
of those
那些
alright so I wanted to spend some time
好吧，我想花点时间
on notifications and warnings because we
关于通知和警告，因为我们
there's actually a considerable amount
实际上有相当数量
of subtle issues that that come up here
这里出现的细微问题
but as I said in the beginning the main
但正如我在一开始所说的
purpose of deprecation is to communicate
弃用的目的是传达
is to provide communication between the
是为了提供
maintainer zuv the API and the consumers
维护者zuv API和使用者
of the API and if they're changes in
API的版本以及是否在
status of something then the the users
然后用户的状态
of the API developers need to be
API开发人员需要
informed of this so you know if their
知道这一点，所以你知道他们是否
problems with the API or if it's going
API出现问题或运行不正常
to go away but but that's that's the
走开，但这就是
general point here is how to communicate
这里的一般要点是如何交流
these information through the API so one
这些信息是通过API实现的
of the problems is we say okay well
问题是我们说很好
write some words in the specification
在规范中写一些话
that says oh there's a problem with this
说哦，这有问题
and therefore we're going to take it
因此，我们要接受它
away well I shouldn't say nobody reads
很好，我不应该说没人读
the documentation but there's a large
文档，但是有很多
class of people who who don't read the
那些不读
documentation but the fact is if some
文档，但事实是
some note like that is buried in the
像这样的音符被埋在
documentation you know I know what that
你知道的文件我知道那是什么
method does all right I don't need to
方法可以，我不需要
read the documentation last year I don't
我去年不读文档
I don't you know I'm not going to it's
我不知道我不会去的
unreasonable to expect developers to go
期望开发人员去不合理
through with fine-tooth comb and say oh
用细齿梳子说哦
this clause was added here that says
此条款在此处添加，内容为
this you know this this method is is
这个你知道这个方法是
going to be deprecated so we need some
将被弃用，所以我们需要一些
some some stronger more reliable form of
一些更强大更可靠的形式
communicating this information to
将此信息传达给
developers so there's several different
开发人员，所以有几种不同的
ways of doing this and so the first is
这样的方式，所以第一个是
compile time notification this is the
编译时间通知，这是
one that we should be familiar with
我们应该熟悉的一种
already if you if you write a program
如果您编写程序已经
that uses a deprecated API then the
使用不推荐使用的API，然后
compiler will issue warning about that
编译器将发出警告
and there are various there are some
有各种各样的东西
wrinkles here about the severity the
皱纹的严重程度
morning whether it's on or off by
早上是开还是关
default and also how to suppress
默认以及如何抑制
warnings that you that you know that you
警告你，你知道你
are aware of but that you do not want to
知道但您不想
deal with right now but then there are
现在处理，但随后有
also two new kinds of notification that
还有两种新的通知
we're working on static analysis is
我们正在进行静态分析
useful because the fact is you get the
有用，因为事实是您得到了
compiler warnings only when you
仅当您使用编译器警告时
recompile everything and in fact we we
重新编译一切，实际上我们
don't expect people to recompile
不要期望人们重新编译
the point is the point one of the big
重点是重点之一
points of Java is binary compatibility
Java的要点是二进制兼容性
you can take your old binaries and
您可以使用旧的二进制文件
continue to run them and so this is the
继续运行它们，所以这是
biggest hole in notification and
通知中的最大漏洞
deprecation because thus far the only
弃用，因为到目前为止
kind of notification is compile time
通知的类型是编译时间
warnings so if you have an old binary
警告，如果您有旧的二进制文件
that is using a deprecated API you never
使用从未使用过的API
hear about it unless unless you unless
听说，除非你除非
there's some alternative path so so
有一些替代途径，所以
we're introducing a static analysis tool
我们正在介绍一个静态分析工具
which I'll provide some more details on
我将提供有关的更多详细信息
later to help with that and then another
以后再帮忙
idea which is not implemented at this
这个想法还没有实现
time is to track usage of deprecated
时间是跟踪已弃用的用法
api's at runtime and then provide
api在运行时，然后提供
runtime warnings when one of those is
其中之一是运行时警告
actually called and so for instance you
实际打电话给你，例如
might have a binary that references a
可能具有引用一个
deprecated API but in fact it might be
不推荐使用的API，但实际上可能是
in dead code so if it never calls it who
死代码，所以如果它从不叫它，谁
cares but so on the other hand you might
在乎，但另一方面，您可能
have something that calls that calls an
有一些叫的东西
api reflectively and that will be missed
api反光的，那将被错过
by static analysis but that could be
通过静态分析，但这可能是
potentially picked up by dynamic
有可能被动态拾取
analysis so dynamic analysis is feature
分析，因此具有动态分析功能
work that's not going to be in Java 9
Java 9不会做的工作
all right quick example of a compiler
好的编译器快速示例
warning if you use the deprecated API
如果使用不推荐使用的API，则会发出警告
the first thing you get if you don't
如果不这样做，你会得到的第一件事
provide any options other than the
提供除
default is a note it says you can read
默认是一条便条，上面写着您可以阅读
it there recompile with- excellent
它在那里重新编译-非常好
deprecation for further details and so
弃用以获得更多详细信息，等等
if you do recompile with- excellent
如果您确实重新编译-非常好
deprecation that enables detailed
弃用可实现详细信息
warnings and you get a listing of exact
警告，您会得到确切的清单
the exact line in position where the
确切的位置
deprecated API was used all right I
我使用了不赞成使用的API
think I explained this already but the
认为我已经解释了这个，但是
problem is that if you have an old
问题是，如果你有一个老
binary you just use it you don't
二进制文件，您只用它，不用
recompile it so this old binary might
重新编译它，以便这个旧的二进制文件可能
have uses of deprecated api's in it and
在其中使用了已弃用的api，并且
you might like to know that especially
您可能想知道这一点
if those deprecated api's are going to
如果那些不赞成使用的api将
be removed and so if you just keep using
被删除，所以如果您继续使用
that old binary and then you move on to
那旧的二进制文件，然后您继续
the next JDK release something might
下一个JDK版本可能会
have been deprecated deprecated for
已弃用
removal and then and then finally
去除然后再最后
removed if you if you run that old
如果您使用的是旧版本，则将其删除
binary it'll simply break and you might
二进制文件只会破坏，您可能
why no such method error well what
为什么这样的方法没有错误呢？
happened and then you might have to do
发生了，然后您可能需要做
some some you might have to do some
一些，您可能需要做一些
research or investigation and stuff and
研究或调查以及东西和
so I think that's a that's a nasty
所以我认为那是一个讨厌的
surprise we want to we want to get
惊喜，我们想要，我们想要得到
information about that out to developers
有关此信息的信息提供给开发人员
more in advance of that instead of
在此之前，而不是
having people try things out and then
让人们尝试一下，然后
uncover uncover problems like that when
揭露诸如此类的问题
errors occur in particular it seems like
特别是发生错误
the the way the ecosystem is evolving is
生态系统的发展方式是
if i have an application i might go i
如果我有申请，我可能会去
might use maven and it pulls down a
可能会使用Maven并拉低
bunch of dependent libraries so not only
一堆依赖库，所以不仅
as as if I were an application developer
就像我是应用程序开发人员一样
I have to be concerned about what my
我要担心我的
application is using but also the
应用程序正在使用，但
dependent libraries and they're
依赖库，它们是
dependent libraries as well and so if
依赖库也是如此，如果
those use deprecated AP is then I'm
那些使用过时的AP的人就是
going to want to know about that because
想知道这一点，因为
either I can get those guys to fix make
要么我可以让那些家伙修复
fixes upstream or I can remove my
修复上游或我可以删除我的
dependencies on those libraries so the
对这些库的依赖
point of this is so that developers can
这是为了让开发人员可以
better manage what's going on with their
更好地管理他们的情况
dependent libraries without having to
依赖库，而不必
recompile actually this is this is far
实际重新编译，这是到目前为止
too much detail I just went through this
我刚刚经历了太多细节
in in a sketch here but but suppose I
在这里素描，但我想
have some old class so so that the
有一些老阶级，以便
central issue here is what happens to
这里的中心问题是发生了什么
programs as they evolve and as API
程序随着API的发展而发展
you've api's evolve so suppose I have an
您的api不断发展，所以假设我有一个
application and I compile it against one
应用程序，我将其编译为一个
release of the JDK and it uses some
JDK版本，它使用了一些
api's and everything works fine there
api和那里一切正常
are no warnings now in the next Java
在下一个Java中现在没有警告
release something I use gets deprecated
发布我使用的东西被弃用
but if I don't recompile I never find
但是如果我不重新编译，我永远找不到
out about that and then in the following
关于这一点，然后在下面
JDK release it changes to a terminal
JDK发布将其更改为终端
deprecation deprecated for removal true
弃用不建议移除
and I'm if I'm still running the old
如果我还在运行旧的
binary I never hear about that and so
我从未听说过二进制文件，所以
what I so when I upgrade to the to the
当我升级到
subsequent JDK release after that thing
在那之后的后续JDK版本
actually is removed and I run my
实际上被删除，我运行我的
application and it says no class def
应用程序，它说没有类定义
found error or no such method error or
发现错误或没有此类方法错误或
something like that so that's really an
像这样的东西，这真的是
unpleasant surprise that we're trying to
我们正在尝试令人不愉快的惊喜
avoid here all right so i talked about
避免在这里好吧，所以我谈到
static analysis there's a tool called j
静态分析，有一个叫做j的工具
pepper scan which I developed which is
我开发的胡椒扫描是
introduced in jdk 9 and it is also
在jdk 9中引入，它也是
available in any of the i have a link at
可在任何我有一个链接在
the end with the link to the early
链接到早期的结尾
access builds so you can try it out
访问构建，以便您可以尝试
alright so here's a sample program that
好了，这是一个示例程序
it doesn't do anything interesting all
它没有任何有趣的事情
it does is use ap is that were
它确实是使用ap是
deprecated in various jdk releases and
在各种jdk版本中已弃用，并且
so this list jlist get selected values
所以这个列表jlist获得选定的值
was okay so none of these were
还可以，所以这些都不是
deprecated all of these api's existed in
不推荐使用所有存在于这些API中的API
java 6 and earlier and and none of them
Java 6和更早版本，并且都不是
were deprecated in java 6 in java 7
在Java 7中的Java 6中已弃用
jlist get selected values is deprecated
jlist获取选择的值已弃用
in java 8 the rmi security manager was
在Java 8中，rmi安全管理器是
deprecated and in java 9 as i mentioned
不推荐使用，并且在我提到的Java 9中
earlier the boolean constructor was
较早的布尔构造函数是
deprecated so what's the the interesting
过时了，有趣的是什么
point about this example is that
关于这个例子的重点是
different api's were different were
不同的API是不同的
deprecated different points in time
弃用了不同的时间点
where what time being measured by JDK
JDK在什么时间测量
releases so if I took this sample
发布，所以如果我拿这个样本
program and compiled it using jdk six i
程序并使用jdk 6 i对其进行编译
would get a class file that has
将得到一个具有
references to these methods but of
引用这些方法，但是
course i compiled that on jdk six and it
当然，我在jdk六上编译了它，
compiles great all those api's exist and
可以很好地编译所有这些api的存在，并且
there are no warnings because none of
没有警告，因为没有
them are deprecated in in jdk six so how
他们在JDK 6中已弃用，所以
do we find out about that so if i take
我们能找到答案吗？
jada per scan from a recent jdk nine
每次扫描来自最近的jdk 9的jada
build then it tells me Oh class example
建立然后告诉我哦上课的例子
deprecation uses type java on my
弃用在我的类型上使用java
security manager which is deprecated and
已弃用的安全管理器，
so it runs through the class file does
所以它遍历了类文件
some analysis and finds out what what ap
一些分析，找出什么
is that are deprecated are being
被弃用的是
referenced from this class file and
从此类文件引用，并且
emits messages from that so further
从那里发出消息
feature of JD per scan is that it can
每次扫描JD的功能是它可以
analyze a binary relative to a
分析相对于
particular JDK release so i can add the
特定的JDK版本，因此我可以添加
minus minus release option so i minus
减号减号释放选项，所以我减号
minus release 9 that's the default since
减去版本9，这是默认值，因为
it's being introduced in nine so that
它在九个版本中被引入
gives the same output
给出相同的输出
but if I say Jade deeper scan minus
但是如果我说Jade更深的扫描减去
minus release eight then it only
减去释放八则仅
analyzes that binary for AP is that were
分析AP的二进制文件是
deprecated in Java 8 and earlier and so
在Java 8和更早版本中已弃用，因此
if you notice the difference between
如果您注意到之间的区别
these is that the boolean constructor is
这些是布尔构造函数是
not flagged in the minus release eight
减号8中未标记
output and in fact we can do this for
输出，实际上我们可以这样做
not only for really in JD Kane this is a
不仅是真正的JD Kane，这是
new feature in jdk nine that it has
JDK 9中的新功能
information about AP is that existed in
有关AP的信息存在于
the three prior releases so we can all
三个先前的版本，所以我们都可以
we can go all the way back eight seven
我们可以一路回八七
and six and we can say essentially we're
还有六个，我们可以说我们基本上是
asking the question what deprecated AP
问这个问题什么不赞成使用AP
is does this binary use relative to jdk
相对于jdk，此二进制文件是否使用
version n and so we can say minus
版本n，所以我们可以说减号
release seven and in fact if you go all
释放七，事实上，如果你全力以赴
the way to minors released six none of
未成年人的方式释放了六个没有
these api's were deprecated in six and
这些api的使用时间为6，
so there's no output and so the new
所以没有输出，所以新的
feature here is that the this
这里的特点是
information is built into the jdk and
信息内置到jdk中，
you don't have to carry around old
你不必带老
versions of the GDK in order to do this
版本的GDK为了做到这一点
yeah quick question here okay so the
是的，这里有个快速的问题，所以
question was about the policy of
问题是关于
carrying three versions back so no this
携带三个版本，所以没有这个
this tool is really built on the same
这个工具真的是建立在相同的基础上
compiler tool chain and so this follows
编译器工具链，因此如下
the same policy so in jdk 10 the three
相同的政策，因此在jdk 10中这三个
back will be nine eight and seven and so
后面将是九点八点和七点等等
by the time jdk 10 comes around what
当jdk 10出现时
we're trying to mean so here here's the
我们试图表示的是，这是
end of life process I think we're saying
生命周期结束，我想我们是说
okay jdk six in the jdk ten time frame
好的，在十个时间间隔内，六个
we don't it we don't expect most people
我们不，我们不期望大多数人
to be migrating to jdk six at this point
即将迁移至六
so the point of carrying this old
所以背着这个旧的意义
information around is when jdk 10 comes
周围的信息是jdk 10何时到来
out people will still be migrating from
人们仍然会从
older releases but they won't
较旧的版本，但它们不会
necessarily migrate to the very late
一定要迁移到很晚
just one so when ten is out you might
只有一个，所以当十个出来的时候
want to use the latest tool chains but
想使用最新的工具链，但是
you might be migrating to eight or nine
您可能要迁移到八个或九个
and so that's why we keep that
所以这就是为什么我们保留那个
information around for use but but when
信息可供使用，但何时
something is so old we're just dropping
东西太旧了，我们只是掉线
things off the tail end now I think
现在我想事情从头到尾
we're just we're kind of moving things
我们只是在移动事物
through on a per release basis all right
通过每个版本都可以
so one of the things there's another
所以其中一件事是另外一件事
there's another wrinkle here which which
这里还有另一个皱纹
we actually discovered well fairly
我们实际上发现得很好
recently in this which is there's kind
最近在这是一种
of a new state transition in the API
API中的新状态转换
evolution so the big state transition
进化，所以大的国家过渡
that has been around for a while is from
已经有一段时间了
not deprecated to deprecated but there's
不建议弃用，但有
a potential potential additional issue
潜在的潜在附加问题
which is from an ordinary deprecation to
从普通的弃用到
a terminal deprecation and that's when
最终弃用，那是什么时候
for removal changes from false to true
用于将更改从false更改为true
and so the problem the problem is with
所以问题出在
with an interaction with suppressed
与压抑的互动
warnings and so I have a scenario of
警告，所以我有一个方案
this on the next slide here okay so
这在下一张幻灯片上可以
suppose I have suppose this is this is
假设我想这是这个
relative to compiler warnings so suppose
相对于编译器警告，所以假设
I have an application and it compiles
我有一个应用程序，它可以编译
fine no warnings it uses some AP is that
罚款没有警告，它使用一些AP是
are not deprecated now in some in the
现在不被淘汰
next JDK release an API becomes
下一个JDK版本的API
deprecated all right I recompile it and
不赞成使用，我重新编译它，
I get a deprecation warning and I'm very
我收到了弃用警告，我非常
conscientious so I say okay I am going
认真的所以我说我要走了
to add a suppress warnings annotation to
将抑制警告注释添加到
suppress that to suppress that warning
压制那个警告
because i i'm using a deprecated API but
因为我使用的API已弃用，但
it's not marked for removal but I I want
它没有标记为删除，但我想要
to continue using it so I so add
继续使用它，所以我添加
suppress warnings there then in the next
抑制警告，然后在下一个
JDK release the deprecation is upgraded
JDK版本弃用升级
to for removal equals true so that means
to表示移除等于true，这意味着
this API is going to be removed but when
该API将被删除，但是当
I recompile I already have a suppressed
我重新编译我已经被抑制了
warnings there so I don't get any
警告在那里，所以我什么也没收到
warning when that happens and then when
警告何时发生，然后何时
I recompile on the following JDK release
我在以下JDK版本上重新编译
when the thing is gone it says symbol
当事情不见了，它说符号
not found alright so that's a nasty
没找到好，这很讨厌
surprise because our notification system
惊喜，因为我们的通知系统
has failed us
使我们失败了
so this is this is actually work in
所以这实际上是在
progress now this is not integrated in
进展，现在还没有集成
its jdk nine yet but if you look at the
它的九丹麦克朗，但如果你看看
suppress warnings annotation there's
抑制警告注释
actually a tag there you can put and so
实际上是一个标签，您可以放等等
it's basically a string so right now the
它基本上是一个字符串，所以现在
way to suppress deprecation warnings is
抑制弃用警告的方法是
at suppress warnings deprecation so what
在禁止警告弃用时，那么
we're saying is if you're using a
我们是说如果您使用的是
deprecated api with for removal equals
已弃用的api，用于删除等于
true that is if you are using a
是的，如果您使用的是
terminally deprecated API that's going
即将弃用的API
to fall into a different category
属于不同的类别
warnings and we're calling those removal
警告，我们称这些移除
warnings so so that means that if you've
警告，所以这意味着如果您已经
already suppress the warning for
已经取消警告
ordinary deprecation if that thing
如果那东西普通贬值
becomes terminally deprecated you're
最终被弃用
going to get a warning anyway even
反正会得到警告
though there's a suppressed warnings
尽管有禁止显示的警告
already there and we want that to happen
已经在那里，我们希望做到这一点
because since it if it didn't happen you
因为既然没有发生，那你
missed that notification so if you if
错过了该通知，所以如果您
you are using something that is
您正在使用的是
terminally deprecated and you still want
最终弃用，您仍然想要
to continue using it at your own risk
继续使用，后果自负
because it is going to be removed then
因为它将要被删除
you can suppress that warning using
您可以使用以下方式禁止显示该警告
suppressed warnings removal so that's
禁止删除警告，因此
that's in progress unfortunately that's
不幸的是，那是正在进行的
not that's not in the current EA builds
不是，这不在当前的EA版本中
yet but we're working on it also I think
但是，我认为我们也在努力
I think it's going to turn out this way
我想这会变成这样
if you you remember earlier on I said if
如果你还记得我之前说过
you use the deprecated API you just got
您使用的是刚刚弃用的API
a note and you had to say excellent
一张纸条，你不得不说很棒
excellent deprecation to enable the
出色的弃用功能使
details if you use a terminally
详细信息，如果您使用终端
deprecated api you're going to get the
不推荐使用的api，您将获得
detailed warnings by default instead of
默认情况下显示详细警告，而不是
having to go through a second pass and
必须经过第二遍
reenable them so what we're trying to do
重新启用它们，所以我们正在尝试做
is to have a stronger warning for things
对事物有更强烈的警告
that are deprecated for removal because
不建议将其删除，因为
that's a much more that's much more
不仅如此，还有更多
serious situation because we really do
严重的情况，因为我们确实
intend to remove those all right this is
打算删除那些没事的，这是
a this is a little bit of this is a
这是这个的一点
little bit of old old cleanup work
旧的旧清理工作的一点点
remember i said earlier on that that the
记得我之前说过
original deprecation was a javadoc tag
最初的弃用是javadoc标签
but annotations didn't
但是注释没有
just until Java five so how was it
直到Java 5才怎么样
recorded in the class file all the way
一直记录在类文件中
back in 1.1 thru 1.4 how was it where
回到1.1至1.4
was it recorded that something was
是否有记录是
deprecated so so the way annotations
弃用，所以注释方式
work is when they're compiled they
工作是当他们被编译时
actually end up in the class file and so
实际上是在类文件中结束的，所以
today deprecated api's have a deprecated
今天已弃用的api已弃用
annotation that actually ends up in the
最终以
class file and the compilers look the
类文件，编译器看起来
filers and ID's look for that annotation
文件管理器和ID查找该注释
and may issue warnings when they
并可能在他们发出警告时发出警告
discover uses but before annotation is
发现用途，但在注释之前
this that before annotations existed
这在注释存在之前
where was that information recorded well
信息在哪里记录得很好
it turns out if you look in the if you
事实证明，如果您看着
look in the JVM specification there's
在JVM规范中
something called the deprecated
所谓的过时的东西
attribute that's different from the
该属性与
deprecated javadoc tag and that's
不推荐使用的javadoc标记，那就是
different from the deprecated annotation
与不建议使用的注释不同
and so that's this little thing in there
这就是那里的小东西
in fact it has no information it is
实际上它没有任何信息
essentially a boolean that says this API
本质上说此API的布尔值
is deprecated and so that is still
已弃用，因此仍然
around because that's how the original
周围，​​因为那是原始的
deprecation mechanism worked all dating
弃用机制适用于所有约会
all the way back to 1.1 all right so
一路回到1.1好吧
here we are Java 5 introduced
这里我们介绍Java 5
annotations annotations are now the
注释注释现在是
preferred way of marking something
标记事物的首选方式
deprecated so what are we going to do
弃用了，我们该怎么办
with the deprecated class file attribute
具有不推荐使用的类文件属性
I think we're going to deprecate it so
我认为我们将弃用
so this is this is the long term
所以这是长期的
evolution here I am there's actually no
我在这里进化实际上没有
way to deprecate things from a class
从类中弃用事物的方法
file I think so might be one of these
我认为可能是这些文件之一
things where in the next version of the
在下一个版本中
the JVM class file format it will
它将使用的JVM类文件格式
actually be removed from the
实际上从
specification and the semantics of class
规范和类的语义
file attributes are if you are
文件属性是
processing a class file then you ignore
处理一个类文件，然后忽略
attributes that that you know nothing
你一无所知的属性
about and so I think we haven't worked
关于，所以我认为我们没有工作
this out entirely and it's probably not
完全是这样，可能不是
going to occur in jdk 9 so in a future
将会在jdk 9中发生，所以将来
jdk release their will i suspect we
JDK释放他们我会怀疑我们
might end up with a situation where a
最终可能会遇到以下情况：
future class file version will no longer
将来的课程文件版本将不再
have the deprecated attribute in it and
具有已弃用的属性，并且
so the deprecation information will
因此，弃用信息将
reside solely in annotations
仅驻留在注释中
alright so future work I mentioned
好吧，我提到的未来工作
earlier that one of the things we want
早些时候，我们想要的一件事
to do going forward is to develop
要做的就是发展
runtime analysis tool I think the main
我认为主要是运行时分析工具
thing there is that there's a lot of
事情是，有很多
things out there that that do reflective
反射出来的东西
access to things and those will be
访问事物，那些将是
missed by the static analyzer there are
静态分析仪错过了
a fair number of AP is in the queue to
大量的AP正在排队
be deprecated in particular legacy
在特定遗产中不推荐使用
collections like vector hash table and
像矢量哈希表和
enumeration optional dot get that that
枚举可选点得到
caused a lot of consternation when I
当我引起很多惊ster
proposed that I believe there are some
建议我相信有一些
issues with that it's actually quite
问题是，实际上
error-prone in fact I did a survey of
容易出错，实际上我对
JDK code and found that most uses of
JDK代码，发现大多数用途
optional get were better rewritten to
可选的get最好重写为
avoid using it there's some old things
避免使用它有一些旧东西
like timer and timer task which has been
例如计时器和计时器任务
superseded by threats scheduled
被预定的威胁取代
threadpool executor it's kind of a
线程执行器，有点像
mouthful and then Dayton calendar are
一口，然后代顿日历是
now obsolete because we have the new
现在已经过时，因为我们有了新的
Java time API is introduced in eight so
Java Time API的八点介绍
it's time to time to step up the
现在是时候加强
deprecation for date and calendar one of
弃用日期和日历之一
the problems though is actually no I
问题其实不是我
talked about warnings on the next slide
在下一张幻灯片中讨论了警告
so sorry current work java korba module
所以对不起目前的工作java korba模块
and there's a question mark here because
这里有一个问号，因为
it hasn't happened yet we do we we feel
它还没有发生
like we want to deprecate korba and but
就像我们想弃用科巴，但
it is a fairly recent change to jig saw
这是对曲线锯的一个相当近期的变化
in that the module info Java syntax up
在那模块信息Java语法上
until fairly recently has not supported
直到最近还不支持
annotations and so what do you do if you
注释，如果您要怎么办
want to deprecate a module and so the
想要弃用模块，因此
jigsaw team has been working on some
拼图团队一直在努力
stuff and they recently have decided to
的东西，他们最近决定
make a syntactic change to allow
进行语法更改以允许
annotations on a module declaration in
在模块声明中的注释
module info Java for the express purpose
Java模块信息
of using the deprecated annotation so
使用不推荐使用的注释的原因
that made me very happy all right so one
那让我很开心，所以一个
of the stumbling blocks with deprecating
弃用的绊脚石
all those api's is that they in fact are
所有这些api其实是
in widespread use and then adding
广泛使用，然后添加
deprecation 'he's will create compiler
弃用他将创建编译器
warnings
警告
and that's actually a problem for the
这实际上是一个问题
JDK itself because there are lots of
JDK本身，因为有很多
uses of things like vector in the JDK
在JDK中使用诸如vector之类的东西
and so we would have to do a lot more
所以我们将不得不做更多的事情
warnings clean up if we deprecated
如果我们不推荐使用，警告会清除
vector so on the one hand yeah we want
向量，一方面，我们想要
to deprecate the old stuff and and you
弃用旧东西，而你
know mark it as old and obsolete at the
知道将其标记为旧且已过时
same time it's going to create lots and
同时它将创造很多
lots of work for us because we have lots
我们有很多工作，因为我们有很多
of warnings cleanup to do so and then a
清除警告，然后再执行
lot of people on the open JDK mailing
很多人在打开JDK邮件
lists complained about this as well and
清单也对此抱怨
rightfully so because you know they
没错，因为你知道他们
don't like nobody likes it when somebody
不喜欢有人时不喜欢
else creates work for them and so but
其他为他们创造工作，所以但是
what I take away from this is that we
我从中得到的是，我们
need to provide better mechanisms for
需要提供更好的机制
managing warnings so there's a variety
管理警告，所以有各种各样的
of things like suppress warnings minus
抑制警告减去
excellent options and so forth that can
优秀的选择等等可以
help with this but they're not powerful
对此有所帮助，但它们并不强大
enough so we have some ideas of maybe
足够，所以我们对
doing API specific warnings management
执行API特定的警告管理
or something like that that's all it's
或类似的东西就足够了
all just ideas nothing implemented that
所有的想法都没有实现
yet all right so the conclusion here is
还好，所以这里的结论是
that oh there's a JEP for deprecation
哦，有一个JEP要弃用
Jeff is JDK enhancement proposal so Jeff
Jeff是JDK的增强建议，因此Jeff
277 is almost completed basically it
277基本就完成了
consists of upgraded the upgrade to the
包括升级到
deprecated annotation itself new
不推荐使用的注解本身是新的
depredations for AP is and then the JD
AP的折旧，然后是JD
per scan tool so we're slowly cleaning
每个扫描工具，所以我们要慢慢清洁
up the API in the JDK and we're also in
JDK中的API，我们也在
progress is is this new warnings
进展是这个新的警告
category suppress warnings removal there
类别禁止删除警告
a couple links there for a link to the
一对夫妇在那里链接到
JEP and the recent JDK nine builds all
JEP和最近的JDK 9版本全部构建
of these have the J diaper scan tool in
其中有J尿布扫描工具
them so I encourage you to go download
他们，所以我鼓励你去下载
it and try it out so i'm on twitter i
并尝试一下，所以我在推特上我
have a couple twitter handles here i am
我在这里有几个推特手柄
dr. deprecated ur on Twitter and my real
博士在Twitter和我的真实网站上弃用了ur
name is Stuart marks so you can talk to
名字是斯图尔特商标，所以你可以和
me talk to me directly that way so thank
我直接这样跟我说话，谢谢
you and I we have a few minutes left for
你和我还有几分钟的时间
questions there's a question right here
问题这里有一个问题
this gentleman
这个绅士
oh thank you hmm yes okay so the
哦，谢谢，嗯，是的，所以
question was about third-party libraries
问题是关于第三方库
excellent question i actually forgot i
我实际上忘记了一个很好的问题
was intending to put put something like
打算把像
this in my presentation but i forgot
这在我的演讲中，但我忘了
about it so so right now the deprecation
关于它，所以现在就弃用
stuff is kind of JDK centric which is
东西是一种以JDK为中心的
maybe what you're what you're thinking
也许你在想什么
about so in so any third-party library
在任何第三方库中都差不多
can use the deprecated annotation but
可以使用不推荐使用的注释，但是
the scanner tool only supports scanning
扫描仪工具仅支持扫描
for jdk AP is and so what I envision is
对于jdk AP是，所以我的设想是
to have a more complex mode where the
拥有更复杂的模式
tool can gather deprecation information
工具可以收集弃用信息
from this library and then with that
从这个库中，然后
information analyze this binary here for
信息在这里分析此二进制文件
uses of an api of deprecated api's from
api的使用已过时
that library so yes I mean that's in the
该图书馆，是的，我的意思是在
plan but thats future work at this point
计划，但那是未来的工作
question right here so
在这里提问
standard
标准
will it perform that this library is
它会执行该库是
using that because of deprecation
因为弃用而使用它
okay good question question was if
好的，好的问题是
something if an API has been removed
如果已删除API
does the scanner tool does the scanner
扫描仪工具会做扫描仪吗
tool report that because that thing is
工具报告，因为那件事是
is simply gone from the API now and
现在已经从API中消失了，
that's a good question i'll have to
这是一个很好的问题，我必须
think some more about that case because
想更多有关该案例的信息，因为
i actually have not considered that case
我实际上没有考虑过这种情况
very well because I are you know we
很好，因为我是你，我们知道
don't have a track record of having
没有过往的记录
removed stuff so we don't have an
删除了东西，所以我们没有
experience of how to cope with something
如何应付某事的经验
that's already been removed so good
已经被删除了，很好
question okay okay right okay all right
问题好吧好吧好吧好吧好吧
okay so so there's there's there's some
好，所以那里有一些
I have a partial answer here which is so
我在这里有一个部分答案是
the release option for JD per scan reads
每次扫描的JD释放选项读取
the internal tables from the compiler
编译器的内部表
toolchain where which which has recorded
已记录的工具链
all passed well not all the three
一切都通过得很好
releases of past API information so the
过去的API信息的发布，因此
way I envisioned J depre scan working
我设想的J depre扫描工作方式
for third-party libraries is certainly
第三方库肯定是
we're not going to ship those in the JDK
我们不会在JDK中发货
right we're not going to maintain
对，我们不会维持
information about past deprecation for
有关过去的折旧的信息
third-party libraries but one of the
第三方库，但其中之一
modes in fact it sort of there's a
模式实际上有点
there's a vestige in there right now for
现在那里有痕迹
experimental purposes is to scan a
实验目的是扫描
library and record the deprecation
记录并记录折旧
information and so if if your developer
信息，如果您的开发人员
who's using a third-party library then
谁在使用第三方库
you can scan that library and simply
您可以扫描该库并简单地
record its deprecated information so if
记录其过时的信息，以便
you have multiple versions of that
你有多个版本
library you can record separate
您可以单独记录的库
databases for that and then when you
数据库，然后当你
want to do analysis you can say well I
想做分析你可以说我
want to use I want to use version 3 4
我想使用版本3 4
here to see to see what was deprecated
在这里看到什么不推荐使用
in version 3 vs version 4 version 5
在版本3与版本4和版本5中
whatever whatever versions that you
不管你用什么版本
recorded from the third party library
从第三方库记录
now actually this is very interesting
现在实际上这很有趣
you
您
you if you've done some thinking about
如果您已经考虑过
this I'd like to talk to you afterwards
之后我想和你谈谈
to see whether that that works or
看看是否可行
whether there's an alternative approach
是否有替代方法
necessary or something like that so
必要或类似的东西
let's move on
让我们继续
so so that the the tool output right now
这样工具现在就输出
is I think you must have read the
我想你一定是读过
documentation or something because
文档或其他原因
because because they thought there is a
因为因为他们以为有一个
line in there which I wrote which said
我写的那行说
the the output is for informational
输出仅供参考
purposes only but what I was referring
只是目的，但我指的是
to before is kind of this experimental
之前是这种实验
API or experimental function where it
API或实验功能在哪里
would the the scan results would be
扫描结果将是
recorded in some well-defined format
以明确定义的格式记录
that could be kept around and I think
可以保留下来，我认为
the idea is that that instead of being
这个想法是，而不是
for informational purposes that be kept
仅供参考
in in a a format that is machine
以机器形式的aa格式
readable and possible so the deprecation
可读且可能因此弃用
information from some old library can be
一些旧图书馆的信息可以
kept around indefinitely now if in that
现在无限期地徘徊
old library you deprecated something for
您不赞成使用的旧图书馆
removal true then I think you need some
去除是真的，我想你需要一些
kind of project management workflow or
种类的项目管理工作流程或
something so that when the next release
以便下次发布时
comes around you're going to have to say
到处走，你不得不说
okay look in that list of things that we
好吧，看一下我们列出的东西
said where we set for removal true and
说我们设置要删除的位置为true和
make sure actually to remove them and so
确保将其删除，如此
so so it's not all there yet this is
所以还不是全部，这是
like the first release of the tool but
像该工具的第一个版本一样，
in principle yes it should be possible
原则上是应该有可能
to to record that information and then
记录该信息，然后
enable a future version of yourself or
启用自己的未来版本或
your successor to look at that and say
你的继任者看看那个并说
okay these are the things that we now
好的，这些就是我们现在所要做的
need to remove because they were
需要删除，因为它们是
deprecated okay I think this gentleman
我认为这位先生已经过时了
has been waiting for long
已经等了很久了
to force a good program practice what do
强迫良好的程序实践做什么
you think the effects are good program
你认为效果很好
practice will be now that there's really
现在的实践是
ah so so the question was initially that
嗯，所以问题最初是
that that the ambiguity is good because
歧义性很好，因为
it helped further better programming
它有助于进一步更好地编程
practices and I I I don't know I mean I
习俗和III不知道我的意思是我
I don't like ambiguity but then since
我不喜欢含糊不清
this is since this is really this is
这是因为这真的是
this is really sort of bridging over
这真的是桥接
into kind of a non technical aspect
进入非技术方面
where I mean this is this is maintenance
我的意思是这就是维护
this is life cycle stuff this is not you
这是生命周期的东西，这不是你
know there's a bug in this program or
知道该程序中存在错误或
there is not a bug in this program so so
该程序没有错误，因此
it's hard to boil that down to a binary
很难把它煮成二进制
at the same time it's harder to come up
同时很难出现
with a finer gradation or something like
具有更好的渐变或类似的东西
that that's still useful so what effect
那仍然有用，什么效果
is this going to have on on engineering
这将在工程上继续吗
best practices I don't know my hope is
我不知道的最佳实践是
that it will improve things I think that
它将改善我认为的事情
my my view is that the ambiguity was was
我的观点是模棱两可是
was damaging because you know like I go
之所以破坏是因为你知道我要走了
back to this conversation on some
回到这个对话上
internet forum where people are saying
人们在说互联网论坛
uh deprecation doesn't mean anything
de贬不算什么
they'll never remove anything somebody
他们永远不会删除任何人
else's well then they might they might
否则，他们可能会
remove it what if they do right and and
如果他们做对了，该怎么办？
so so I think uncertainty is is doing
所以我认为不确定性正在发生
some damage there and so so I think by
那里有些损坏，所以我想
clarifying this I mean even even though
澄清这个我的意思是即使
it's only one boolean but by adding this
它只是一个布尔值，但是通过添加
literally bit of clarification then that
字面上的澄清然后
will that will remove some of these you
会删除一些你吗
know you know how internet arguments
知道你知道互联网的争论
good you can never win an internet
好，你永远不会赢得互联网
argument they just go on until they
他们只是继续争论直到他们
until they decide not to and so I'm
直到他们决定不这样做，所以我
hoping that this will that this will
希望这将这将
will will take a certain subset of those
将采取其中的某些子集
internet arguments and and say this is
互联网争论，并说这是
the answer it's going to be removed and
答案将被删除，
then there's going to be a different
那么将会有一个不同的
argument about well when is it going to
关于什么时候去的争论
be removed okay I that gentleman back
好吧，我那位先生回来了
there
那里
yeah question about whether the text of
是的，关于
the warnings will be different whether
警告是否会有所不同
something is for removal true or false
去除真假的东西
we're working on that yeah I think what
我们正在努力，是的，我想
we need to do is make sure that that it
我们需要做的就是确保它
is absolutely clear that if you use a
绝对清楚，如果您使用
deprecated API whether it's ordinary or
不推荐使用的API，无论是普通的还是
terminal deprecation that the the text
终端弃用该文本
of the of the output that you get makes
您获得的输出的
it absolutely clear what you know what
绝对清楚你知道什么
the disposition of that thing is and so
那东西的处置是这样的
yeah so that's that's something we need
是的，那就是我们需要的东西
to work on I still need to I have a I
要继续工作，我仍然需要一个I
have a bug I need to fix which is
我需要修复一个错误
basically you know take a relook at the
基本上，你知道看看
Jade a purse can output and make sure
玉皮钱包可以输出并确保
that make sure those messages are right
确保这些消息正确
and i'm working with a compiler team to
我正在与一个编译器团队合作
make sure that their warnings are
确保他们的警告是
appropriate as well so I think I'm out
也合适，所以我想我出去了
of time at this point so thank you for
在这一点上的时间，所以谢谢
your interest and attention and I'll be
您的关注和关注，我会
hanging around a little bit so there are
徘徊一点所以有
few more questions all right thanks very
还好几个问题，非常感谢
much
许多